

Fábio Gonçalves

Web Developer



Github https://github.com/fabi0wz



Digital CV/Portfolio fabi0wz.github.io



Contact 936 270 893



Email fabiomiguel3.10@gmail.com



LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/fabiowz/

SUMMARY



I am currently pursuing a CET in Information Systems Programming at ATEC. I have experience in graphic design and web design, and I am proficient in Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, XD, and Lightroom. And I'm now starting my career in software development

TECH STACK



Front-end Development:

HTML CSS, Bootstrap JavaScript

Back-end Development:

C#

C++

PHP, and Laravel Framework
T-SQL (and MySQL language), relational DB's

Other Technologies:

Git

Linux (operating system)
Apache (web server)
REST APIs (building and consuming)

PERSONAL SKILLS



Experience in UI and Design Knowledge in Windows and Linux servers Diagnostics and repairing of computers

EDUCATION



Specialized Technician in Information Systems Programming

QNQ 5 - ATEC 2022-Atualmente

Multimedia Technician

QNQ 4 - Escola Secundária Abel Salazar 2012-2016

HISTORY



Grupo GP

Production/Logistics Operator 15/10/2022 - Current

MarqueTDI

Production Operator 23/03/2022 - 07/10/2022

Staples

Image and Printing Specialist 11/02/2019 - 25/08/2021

LANGUAGES



English Portuguese